Egemen Ton

Funverse Games

Beylikduzu/Istanbul | +905385022224 | egementon98@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/egementon/ @ egemen.hicaku.com

Summary

I am a passionate gamer and a game developer. After graduating as a Physics Engineer at one of the top schools in Turkey, I decided to follow my real passion, game development.

I have one year of experience with game programming using Unreal Engine. I live with the dream of making games worth the players' time and offering them unforgettable experiences, similar to the experiences I am having with my favorite games.

Experience

Gameplay Programmer Intern

02/2023 - NOW

Funverse Games

I am working on player abilities for a MOBA game called Hit&Boom using Unreal Engine and its framework Gameplay Ability System (GAS). Earlier in my internship, I started learning GAS and made a small project. After completing it successfully, I started working on the game itself. Currently, I am prototyping new skills according to the design document and working on making them game-ready.

Undergraduate Research Assistant

09/2021 - 07/2022

ITU Nanomechanics Laboratory

I investigated the mechanical properties of graphene structures by scanning surfaces with Atomic Force Microscope.

Intern 08/2020 - 09/2020

TUBITAK - National Metrology Institute

I tested a specific machine to see if it complies with the standards.

Education

Physics Engineering (B.S.)

2016 - 2022

Istanbul Technical University

GPA: 2.97

Relevant Coursework: Symbolic and Numerical Techniques in Physics (C++, Matlab), Computational Analysis of Physical Systems (Python), Introduction to Programming Language (Fortran)

Thesis Title: "Exploring New Methods to Mechanically Exfoliate Graphene and Examining the Cleavage Energy of Graphite", "Applications of Atomic Force Microscopy"

Certificates

• DIGIAGE Oyun Geliştirme Yaz Kampı & Global Ekosistem Buluşması Katılım Sertifikası (1-11 September 2022)

Udemy:

- Learn C++ for Game Development
- Unreal Engine 5 C++ Developer: Learn C++ & Make Video Games
- Unreal Engine C++ The Ultimate Shooter Course
- The Ultimate Git Course with Applications in Unreal Engine



Skills

Game Development, Unreal Engine, C++, Blueprint, Gameplay Programming, Gameplay Ability System (GAS), Git

Portfolio

My website

If it doesn't work, please use this link.

Hobbies & Activities

- Playing video games
- I am a self-taught piano and electric guitar player who composes music
- Reading sci-fi/fantasy books
- Watching movies
- Sprinting as a runner in the university athletics team
- As a volunteer, I was responsible for feeding campus animals and taking care of their needs.